iwindsurf.com 2019-06-05

# Privacy Policy – WeatherFlow Support

**All Information Confidential**

We collect information from our members during the registration process and, occasionally, at other times. This information, which ranges from limited personal data such as age and address to facts about members' equipment, ability and windsurfing habits, is then securely stored and will always remain confidential.

**Uses of Registration Information**  
Registration information may be used in several ways: To enable us to process, validate and verify paid memberships; To provide advertisers with aggregate - never individual - information about our member base and usage patterns; To give us information that's useful for developing new features and services that meet member needs; To allow us to potentially vary the advertising that members see based on their personal information.

**Research**  
We may conduct occasional online surveys. If you choose to participate, you'll be prompted to answer a series of online questions. Your responses are confidential and will be used for statistical analysis only; no information on an individual's preferences will be shared with any outside organization.

**Cookie Technology**  
We employ cookie technology to help members move faster through our site. When a member signs on to our website we may pass a cookie to that user's computer. A cookie is a string of information that's sent by a Web site and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. This avoids the potentially time-consuming task of entering your username and password each time a page is requested.

**Other Key Facts**  
We do not release member names to any outside organizations, which means we do not sell our member list. We do, however, send members e-mail notifications of new site features and promotions for our services. In the future, we may send targeted promotions for third-party products and services which we think are valuable to our members. Only those members who have agreed during registration will receive them. Members may cancel at any time. Finally, we reserve the right to contact any member at any time regarding membership renewals or other membership-related problems or questions.  
**  
Data Security Policy**  
All personal data transmitted through the internet going to and from site registration forms, etc. are protected using industry-standard, 128 bit encryption over the Secure Sockets Layer protocol. Credit Card Information is encrypted, before storage, using highly secure cryptographic algorithms.

**Non-Personalized Ads**  
For the protection of all of our users worldwide (and in Compliance with the EU's General Data Protection Regulation, the GDPR): We display only non-personalized ads on our apps & websites. We do not manipulate the user's individual personal data to determine which ads are served to them. Rather, our ad serving criteria is universal & simple: Kiteboarders see our Kiteboarding ad rotation (such as on iKitesurf.com), Windsurfers see our Windsurfing ad rotation (such as on iWindsurf.com), etc. Also in compliance with the EU regulation, we do not manipulate personal information on children's accounts. Finally, our advertising program is organic and run in-house by our own employees -- not by third party outside ad serving entities or data miners.

**Email Policy  
**Our email policy is very simple: We will NOT send email to anyone who has not opted to receive the email.
